{
  "0": {
    "id": "0",
    "question": "()青水",
    "correct": "清",
    "a1": "氵",
    "a2": "日",
    "a3": "忄",
    "a4": "目",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a1_png",
    "p1": "b1_png",
    "p2": "b2_png",
    "p3": "b3_png",
    "p4": "b4_png"
  },
  "1": {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "()青天",
    "correct": "晴",
    "a1": "日",
    "a2": "讠",
    "a3": "目",
    "a4": "忄",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a2_png",
    "p1": "b2_png",
    "p2": "b5_png",
    "p3": "b4_png",
    "p4": "b3_png"
  },
  "2": {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "事()青",
    "correct": "情",
    "a1": "忄",
    "a2": "氵",
    "a3": "日",
    "a4": "讠",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a3_png",
    "p1": "b3_png",
    "p2": "b1_png",
    "p3": "b2_png",
    "p4": "b5_png"
  },
  "3": {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "眼()青",
    "correct": "睛",
    "a1": "目",
    "a2": "日",
    "a3": "忄",
    "a4": "氵",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a4_png",
    "p1": "b4_png",
    "p2": "b2_png",
    "p3": "b3_png",
    "p4": "b1_png"
  },
  "4": {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "()青求",
    "correct": "请",
    "a1": "讠",
    "a2": "忄",
    "a3": "氵",
    "a4": "目",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a5_png",
    "p1": "b5_png",
    "p2": "b3_png",
    "p3": "b1_png",
    "p4": "b4_png"
  },
  "5": {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "()青蜓",
    "correct": "蜻",
    "a1": "虫",
    "a2": "氵",
    "a3": "忄",
    "a4": "日",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a6_png",
    "p1": "b6_png",
    "p2": "b1_png",
    "p3": "b3_png",
    "p4": "b2_png"
  },
  "6": {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "雨()花",
    "correct": "雪",
    "a1": "彐",
    "a2": "叚",
    "a3": "田",
    "a4": "路",
    "pos": 2,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a7_png",
    "p1": "b7_png",
    "p2": "b11_png",
    "p3": "b9_png",
    "p4": "b10_png"
  },
  "7": {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "秋雨()",
    "correct": "霜",
    "a1": "相",
    "a2": "田",
    "a3": "路",
    "a4": "叚",
    "pos": 2,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a8_png",
    "p1": "b8_png",
    "p2": "b9_png",
    "p3": "b10_png",
    "p4": "b11_png"
  },
  "8": {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "雨()电",
    "correct": "雷",
    "a1": "田",
    "a2": "路",
    "a3": "相",
    "a4": "叚",
    "pos": 2,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a9_png",
    "p1": "b9_png",
    "p2": "b10_png",
    "p3": "b8_png",
    "p4": "b11_png"
  },
  "9": {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "雨()水",
    "correct": "露",
    "a1": "路",
    "a2": "叚",
    "a3": "田",
    "a4": "相",
    "pos": 2,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a10_png",
    "p1": "b10_png",
    "p2": "b11_png",
    "p3": "b9_png",
    "p4": "b8_png"
  },
  "10": {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "晚雨()",
    "correct": "霞",
    "a1": "叚",
    "a2": "彐",
    "a3": "路",
    "a4": "田",
    "pos": 2,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a11_png",
    "p1": "b11_png",
    "p2": "b7_png",
    "p3": "b10_png",
    "p4": "b9_png"
  },
  "11": {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "()寸年",
    "correct": "过",
    "a1": "辶",
    "a2": "又",
    "a3": "日",
    "a4": "木",
    "pos": 3,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a12_png",
    "p1": "b12_png",
    "p2": "b14_png",
    "p3": "b2_png",
    "p4": "b15_png"
  },
  "12": {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "()寸间",
    "correct": "时",
    "a1": "日",
    "a2": "木",
    "a3": "辶",
    "a4": "又",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a13_png",
    "p1": "b13_png",
    "p2": "b15_png",
    "p3": "b12_png",
    "p4": "b14_png"
  },
  "13": {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "反()寸",
    "correct": "对",
    "a1": "又",
    "a2": "辶",
    "a3": "木",
    "a4": "日",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a14_png",
    "p1": "b14_png",
    "p2": "b12_png",
    "p3": "b15_png",
    "p4": "b2_png"
  },
  "14": {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "()寸庄",
    "correct": "村",
    "a1": "木",
    "a2": "日",
    "a3": "又",
    "a4": "辶",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a15_png",
    "p1": "b15_png",
    "p2": "b2_png",
    "p3": "b14_png",
    "p4": "b12_png"
  },
  "15": {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "()也们",
    "correct": "他",
    "a1": "亻",
    "a2": "土",
    "a3": "氵",
    "a4": "目",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a16_png",
    "p1": "b16_png",
    "p2": "b19_png",
    "p3": "b1_png",
    "p4": "b4_png"
  },
  "16": {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "()也们",
    "correct": "她",
    "a1": "女",
    "a2": "氵",
    "a3": "日",
    "a4": "土",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a17_png",
    "p1": "b17_png",
    "p2": "b1_png",
    "p3": "b2_png",
    "p4": "b19_png"
  },
  "17": {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "()也塘",
    "correct": "池",
    "a1": "氵",
    "a2": "亻",
    "a3": "土",
    "a4": "女",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a18_png",
    "p1": "b18_png",
    "p2": "b16_png",
    "p3": "b19_png",
    "p4": "b17_png"
  },
  "18": {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "土()也",
    "correct": "地",
    "a1": "土",
    "a2": "氵",
    "a3": "女",
    "a4": "亻",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a19_png",
    "p1": "b19_png",
    "p2": "b1_png",
    "p3": "b17_png",
    "p4": "b16_png"
  },
  "19": {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "吃()包",
    "correct": "饱",
    "a1": "饣",
    "a2": "足",
    "a3": "氵",
    "a4": "扌",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a20_png",
    "p1": "b20_png",
    "p2": "b22_png",
    "p3": "b1_png",
    "p4": "b23_png"
  },
  "20": {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "()包茶",
    "correct": "泡",
    "a1": "氵",
    "a2": "扌",
    "a3": "火",
    "a4": "足",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a21_png",
    "p1": "b21_png",
    "p2": "b23_png",
    "p3": "b26_png",
    "p4": "b22_png"
  },
  "21": {
    "id": "21",
    "question": "()包步",
    "correct": "跑",
    "a1": "足",
    "a2": "火",
    "a3": "扌",
    "a4": "氵",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a22_png",
    "p1": "b22_png",
    "p2": "b26_png",
    "p3": "b23_png",
    "p4": "b1_png"
  },
  "22": {
    "id": "22",
    "question": "拥()包",
    "correct": "抱",
    "a1": "扌",
    "a2": "衤",
    "a3": "足",
    "a4": "火",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 2,
    "pq": "a23_png",
    "p1": "b23_png",
    "p2": "b27_png",
    "p3": "b22_png",
    "p4": "b26_png"
  },
  "23": {
    "id": "23",
    "question": "()工旗",
    "correct": "红",
    "a1": "纟",
    "a2": "虫",
    "a3": "氵",
    "a4": "扌",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a24_png",
    "p1": "b24_png",
    "p2": "b6_png",
    "p3": "b1_png",
    "p4": "b23_png"
  },
  "24": {
    "id": "24",
    "question": "()工南",
    "correct": "江",
    "a1": "氵",
    "a2": "纟",
    "a3": "扌",
    "a4": "虫",
    "pos": 1,
    "mark": 1,
    "pq": "a25_png",
    "p1": "b25_png",
    "p2": "b24_png",
    "p3": "b23_png",
    "p4": "b6_png"
  }
}